别停下，伙计。
Don't you stop, mate.
给我。
Gimme.
哇哦！一直在玩扑克？
Whoo-hoo! Been playing poker?
你是空军小男孩吗？
You Air Force pussy boys wanna play for cash?
TMD！
Fuck!
我甚至连自己都打不好牌。
I can't even deal myself a good hand.
打赌。我没有了。那么，检查一下。
Bets. I don't have any more. So, check, then.
检查好啊
Check. OK.
那我也会查的。让我们看看你的名片，米奇。
I'll check too, then. Show us your cards, Mikey.
一对皇后。
Pair of Queens.
满屋。
Full house.
我们就叫我有钱人吧！毛拉，伙计！
Let's just call me moneybags! Mullah, man!
还给我，伙计，我需要它。
Give it back, man. I need it.
这不是我的钱。我得去拿我妈妈的处方。
It's not my money. I've gotta pick my mum's prescription up.
如果他输不起，就不要赌博。
Shouldn't gamble if he can't afford to lose it.
别胡闹。把它还给我。
Don't be a shit. Just give it back.
你知道他妈妈病了。你会得到剩下的钱。
You know his mum's sick. You've still got the rest of the money.
好的，我会把你的十块钱还给你。
OK, I'll give you your ten bucks back.
如果…你跳。
If... you jump.
我不能那样做，伙计。我怕高。
I can't do that, man. I-I'm afraid of heights.
岩石会移动。没事的，兄弟。三步走。我们检查了一下。
And the rocks move. It'll be fine, bro. Three steps. We checked it out.
把他妈的钱给我，伙计！什么该死的钱？
Just give me the fucking money, man! What fucking money?
这里的钱都是我的，快吐出来。
Any money around here belongs to me. Cough it up.
你在玩什么，52号接球？走开，维克多。
What are you playing, 52 pick up? Piss off, Victor.
保罗，告诉你哥哥杰克公平地赢得了这笔钱。
Paul, tell your brother Jake won that money fair and square.
闭嘴，败血症。我打你只是为了好玩。
Shut your mouth, septic. I'll bash you just for fun.
你有钱吗？
You got any money?
我们可以打一手。
We could play a hand.
二二三
Two. Two. Three.
三
Three.
好吧…给你看牌。
All right... show you cards.
-一对王牌。-你有什么？
- Pair of Aces. - What've you got?
三个9。走吧，孩子们！
Three nines. Let's go, boys!
操你！
Fuck you!
哦，该死！TMD！
Oh, shit! Fuck!
注意安全，孩子们！
Be safe, boys!
哇！
Whoo!
福利！我他妈的会抓住你的！
Foley! I'll fucking get you!
我他妈的会找到你的！TMD！
I will fucking find you! Fuck!
TMD！
Fuck!
来吧
Come on!
嘿，麦克？是 啊这是你的十美元。为了什么？
Hey, Mikey? Yeah. Here's your tenner. For what?
你跳了！我不是故意的。
You jumped! I didn't mean to.
我在画廊。
I'm at the gallery.
不，不，只是掉了点东西。对不起？
No, no, just dropped something off. Excuse me?
好啊再见
OK? Bye.
是 啊很抱歉
Yeah. Sorry?
不，对不起。这听起来很奇怪，
No, I'm sorry. This is gonna sound really odd,
但我想谢谢你。我在画廊里给你拍了这些照片。
but I wanna thank you. I took these shots of you in the gallery.
我真的很抱歉。
And I really am sorry.
我刚刚看到了你看待艺术的方式。
I just saw the way you were looking at the art.
只是你接受的方式有些问题。
There was just something in the way you were taking it in.
我能请你喝杯咖啡吗？我们能谈谈吗？
Can I buy you a coffee or something? Can we talk?
我不想喝咖啡。你知道阿奇博尔德是什么吗？
I don't want a coffee. Do you know what the Archibald is?
这是肖像奖。是 啊是 啊我想为此画你。
It's a portrait prize. Yeah. Yeah? I wanna paint you for that.
但是，从技术上讲，我们有一段时间在一起。
But, technically, we've gotta spend a bit of time together.
问题是，有一张表格需要签名，我没有，
Thing is, there's a form that needs to be signed, and I don't have it,
但也许…你可以说，
but maybe... you could just say,
“艾丽拉·莫利有权画我的肖像。”
"Alira Morley has permission to paint my portrait."
你只需要说出你的名字。
You just have to say your name.
比赛不会持续六个月，所以我有足够的时间。
The competition's not for six months, so I've got plenty of time.
艾丽拉·莫利有权粉刷我的门廊。
Alira Morley has permission to paint my porch.
好吧，我要走那条路。不，还没有。你得说出你的名字。
OK, I'm gonna go that way. No, not yet. You gotta say your name.
杰克·弗利。
Jake Foley.
你能说出你的年龄和工作吗？可以吗？
Could you maybe say your age and what you do? Is that OK?
我57岁了。
I'm 57.
我是个赌徒。
And I'm a gambler.
这是真的吗？
Is that for real?
你是个赌徒？是 啊
You're a gambler? Yeah.
像运动、马、灰狗之类的？
Like on sports, horses, greyhounds, that kind of thing?
不
No.
我玩扑克。
I play poker.
马上！
Right on!
好吧，谢谢。
Well, thanks.
也许如果我入围了，我会在展览会上见到你？
Maybe if I make the shortlist, I'll see you at the exhibition?
不，你不会的。
No, you won't.
对象不会改变其运动
An object won't change its motion
除非有力作用于它。
Unless a force acts on it.
这是牛顿定律之一。
That's one of Newton's laws.
从我们十几岁的时候起，米奇，亚历克斯。保罗、德鲁和我。
From the time we were teenagers, Mikey, Alex. Paul, Drew and I.
从我们十几岁的时候起，米奇，亚历克斯。保罗、德鲁和我
From the time we were teenagers, Mikey, Alex. Paul, Drew and I
是一群不可分割的海盗。
were an inseparable band of pirates.
但现在很长一段时间，
But for quite a while now,
生活和环境…一直在把我们分开。
Life and circumstance... have been pulling us apart.
施加力的时间不多了
And time is running out to apply the force
那会让我们重归于好。
that would bring us back together.
在所有的男孩中，我最好的朋友是德鲁。
Of all the boys, my best friend was Drew.
我们有很多共同点。我们父亲是空军飞行员，
We had a lot in common. Our dad's were Air Force pilots,
我们喜欢冒险，我们都喜欢纸牌游戏，特别是扑克。
We liked to take risks, and we both love card games, specifically poker.
五张牌抽签，七张牌钉，德州扑克，奥马哈，
Five card draw, seven card stud, Texas Hold'em, Omaha,
Razz、Badugi、Chinese、平局七比七三平，
Razz, Badugi, Chinese, deuce to seven triple draw,
任何类型的扑克。
any kind of poker.
当第一台个人电脑出现时，
When the first personal computers came along,
我们都在考虑，调整它们以适应我们，
we were all over it, adapting them to suit us,
为我们想玩的游戏编写我们自己的程序。
Writing our own programs for the games we wanted to play.
94年，我们建立了世界上第一个在线扑克系统。
And in '94, we set up the world's first online poker system.
当更大的市场向我们靠拢时。。。
When the larger markets opened to us...
当更大的市场向我们开放时
When the larger markets opened to us
那是一个瀑布。
that was a waterfall.
比我们做梦都多的钱。
More money than we'd ever dreamed of.
然后德鲁发现了别的东西。
Then Drew hit on something else.
通过将代码从卡重组到国家，
By restructuring the code from cards to countries,
他重新编排了节目
he retooled the program
成为一款可销售的军用级监控软件。
Into a sale able military grade surveillance software.
我们叫它RIFFLE，该死的名字，我知道。
We called it RIFFLE. Shit name, I know.
我们的客户是政府。
Our customers are governments.
但生活只是一场游戏，对吧？
But life's just a game, right?
这取决于你如何阅读和回应对手。
It's all in how you read and respond to your opponents.
你看他们怎么下注，下注多少。
You watch how they bet, how much they bet.
他们做的每件事都会告诉你更多。
Everything they do informs you more.
如果幸运离你而去，尽你所能改变它的运动。
If luck is leaving you, apply what you can to change its motion.
嘿，我是杰克。
Hey, I'm Jake.
继续走。
Keep walking.
最大限度地赢得胜利，最大限度地减少损失。。。
Maximise your wins, minimise your losses...
最大限度地赢得胜利，最大限度地减少损失，
Maximise your wins, minimise your losses,
尽你所能留在游戏中。
and stay in the game as long as you can.
我是Paje。
I'm Paje.
你可以叫我比尔。满意的。
You can call me Bill. Jake.
是 啊
Yeah.
你带了别的衣服来穿吗？是 啊是 啊
Did you bring something else to wear? Yeah. Yeah.
这是你的空间。
This is your space.
和我一起出去吧。
Join me outside.
药物告诉我你还没准备好。
The medicine is telling me you're not ready yet.
所以我们等待。
So we wait.
如果你愿意，我们可以谈谈。
We can talk if you want.
那我来谈谈。
I'll talk, then.
大多数人来这里…是为了分享经验。
Most people come here... for the shared experience.
数量安全。
Safety in numbers.
共享旅程。
A shared journey.
来这里的人只有三种。
There are only three types of people who come here.
来这里的人只有三种
There are only three types of people who come here
私人预约。
for a private appointment.
有些病态的名人害怕自己的影子。
There's the morbidly famous who are afraid of their own shadow.
毒品被搞砸了
The drug fucked
他错误地认为这是下一个高点。
who quite mistakenly think this is the next great high.
还有不可救药的好奇心。
And the incurably curious.
现在，我认不出你的脸了。
Now, I don't recognise your face.
你看起来并不需要。
You don't appear to be in need.
但你身上有一个重量
But there is a weight on you
而且…这与你的死亡有关。
And... it's related to your mortality.
到目前为止我做得怎么样？
How am I doing so far?
100%.
死亡是不可避免的。
Death is inevitable.
所有生物都会死去。
All living things will die.
你必须宽慰地认识到这一点。
You have to recognise that with relief.
拥抱这些知识。
Embrace that knowledge.
在我的一生中
In my entire life
我花时间思考自己的死亡
the time I've spent pondering my own mortality
如果那样的话，总共会有几分钟。
Would add up to minutes, if that.
也许当我妻子艾莉森去世时，
Maybe when my wife Allison died,
一、 当时我确实问了宇宙很多问题。
I... I did ask the universe a lot of questions then.
我从来没有得到任何满意的答案。
I never got any satisfactory answers.
答案并不总是我们期望的结构。
The answers don't always have the structure we expect.
有时，问题的坚持
Sometimes, the insistence of the question
可能会淹没反应。
Can drown out the response.
我们去解开一些结。
Let's go and untie some knots.
接下来的几年。
The next few years.
在接下来的几天里，总会有人和你在一起。
Over the next few days, there will always be someone here with you.
有时身体想要融合。
Sometimes the body wants to merge.
…是为了你嘴里的东西。
...is for what comes out of your mouth.
你会知道什么时候该喝酒。
You will know when it's time to drink.
拒绝你的问题。。。
Reject the quest for your question...
拒绝你的问题
Reject the quest for your question
到你脑海的前面。
to the front of your mind.
你会知道的
You will know
时间到了。
When it's time.
向自己敞开心扉…是一回事。
Opening up to yourself... is one thing.
向他人敞开心扉可能仍然很困难。
Opening up to others may still be hard.
时机成熟时。。。
When the time's right...
时机成熟时
When the time's right
你也许可以用这个。
you might be able to use this.
这是怎么一回事？
What is it?
让我们称之为真相血清。
Let's just call it a truth serum.
滴几滴，你就会说出你的想法。
A couple of drops and you'll say what's on your mind.
小剂量完全无害。
Perfectly harmless in small doses.
你出汗了，它可以开门。
You're sweating. It can unlock doors.
需要10毫升或更多。。。
It would take 10mls or more...
需要10毫升或更多
It would take 10mls or more
直接注射致死。
directly injected to be lethal.
有些人感到安慰。
Some people take comfort.
有些人感到安慰
Some people take comfort
知道他们有…一些控制手段。
in knowing that they have... some means of control.
磨练这种力量。
Hone that strength.
去
Go!
很好，女孩。在那里休息。
Good, girl. Break there.
准备好的
Ready?
嘿，你。
Hey, you.
你像忍者一样进来了。
You got in here like a ninja.
我一步都没听见，你在干什么？
I didn't hear one step. What are you doing?
只是检查一下房子，确保一切都准备好了。哦
Just checking out the house, making sure everything's ready. Oh.
是的，大型扑克游戏。
Yes, big poker game.
你已经好几年没这么做了。
You haven't done that in years.
是的，他们很忙，我也很忙，仅此而已。
Yeah, well, they've been busy, I've been busy, that's all.
不管怎样，有时和老朋友休息一下
Anyway, taking a break from old friends sometimes
只是提醒你他们对你有多重要。我喜欢那些家伙。
just reminds you how much they mean to you. I love those guys.
他们就像一群犯罪的叔叔一样。
They are just as much my posse of delinquent uncles.
他们就像一群犯罪的叔叔一样
They are just as much my posse of delinquent uncles
因为他们是你的校友。我会确保他们听到的，宝贝。
as they are your school buddies. I will make sure they hear that, baby.
我有一个更严肃的问题。
I have a more serious question.
涉及现金吗？我是你最喜欢的孩子吗
Does it involve cash? Am I your favourite child
最特别的女儿？
and most special daughter?
我可以保证，主要是因为你
I can guarantee that, mainly because you are
我唯一的孩子和女儿。
my only child and only daughter.
嗯，作为你最喜欢的孩子和最特别的女儿，
Hmm. As your favourite child and most special daughter,
街机上有最可爱的牛仔夹克。嗯。
There's the cutest denim jacket down in the arcade. Mm-hm.
所以我想知道。。。
So I was wondering...
是 啊是 啊
Yeah. Yeah.
它比那更可爱。
It's cuter than that.
隐马尔可夫模型。
Hmm.
看看你做了什么。
Look at what you've built.
妈妈会为你感到骄傲的。
Mum would have been so proud of you.
嘿，拜托。。。
Hey, come on...
嘿，拜托
Hey, come on
别让自己难过。
don't get yourself upset.
你妈妈…每天都和我们在一起。
Your mum... is with us every day.
她看到了一切。
She sees everything.
你知道吗，她更愿意看到你笑而不是哭。
And you know what, she'd much rather see you laughing than crying.
我只是想她。
I just miss her.
我不认为没有她我能活一天，
I didn't think I could live... a day without her,
更不用说十年了。
let alone ten years.
满意的。山姆。
Jake. Sam.
我想一下。TMD！
Let me see. Fuck!
现在…如果你决定遗嘱信托，
Now... if you decide on a testamentary trust,
我们知道时间至关重要，
and we know that time is of the essence,
那么你必须提名受托人。那个受托人
then you will have to nominate a trustee. That trustee
可以是个人、组织或信托公司。
can be a person or persons, an organisation or a trust company.
如果你还想探索慈善信托的概念，
If you still wanna explore the idea of a charitable trust,
此外，受托人还必须提名。。。
then, in addition, the trustee will have to nominate...
信任管理员将报告，
The trust administrator will report back,
捍卫受益人的权利。
And defend the rights of your beneficiaries.
听着，我知道这是个大乐透。
Now, look, I know this is a lot to take in.
如果你把结构做对了，伊瓜兰特会像鼓一样紧。
If you do the structure right, I guarantee it'll be tight as a drum.
关于今晚，一切都准备好了。
And in regards to tonight, everything's in place.
十分钟后我会在车库里见到那个家伙。
I'm gonna meet the guys down in the garage in ten minutes.
一旦我做完了，我会在垫子上和你见面。飞行员正在待命。
Once I'm done, I'll meet you at the pad. The pilot's standing by.
好的
Good.
你告诉德鲁了吗？
Have you told Drew?
不是所有的细节，不是。
Not all the details, no.
魔鬼的拥护者。
Devil's advocate.
今晚一切都很复杂，杰克。
Tonight is all very elaborate, Jake.
你确定你想接受吗？
You certain you wanna go through with it?
这一次我不是以你的律师的身份询问。
And this time I'm not asking as your lawyer.
很多人用鲜花和卡片过日子。
Plenty of people get by with flowers and cards.
这可能不是我做过的最好的决定，
Well, they might not be the best decisions I've ever made,
但至少我不会后悔的。
but at least I won't live to regret them.
下面见。
See you down there.
对
Yes.
很抱歉
Sorry.
为何
What for?
这是必要的。
It was necessary.
部长部长今天发布的家庭事务报告。
Minister. Minister. The report on Family Affairs released today.
部长部长今天发布的家庭事务报告
Minister. Minister. The report on Family Affairs released today
似乎与你们部门的声明相矛盾
seems to contradict the stated intentions of your department
就在今年早些时候。贝弗利，你真的在说什么
just earlier this year. Beverly, what you're really saying
媒体是故意误解的吗
is the press contrived to misunderstand
我们去年担任的职位。
the position we took last year.
我所在的部门将低收入家庭的需求放在首位。
My department is putting the needs of lower-income families first.
我知道你个人支持这一点，贝弗利。不，部长。。。
And I know you personally support that, Beverly. No, minister...
部长
Minister!
你收到短信了吗？我们在停车场开会干什么？
Did you get the text? What the fuck are we doing meeting in a car park?
我以为我们在阁楼开会。
I thought we were meeting in the penthouse.
你好，保罗。我也很高兴见到你。
Hello, Paul. Good to see you too.
也许停车场是私人电梯的地方，部长？是 啊
Maybe the car park's where the private lift is, Minister? Yeah,
当然，我们来做吧。
course it is. Let's do this.
你想等亚历克斯吗？塔塞利克可能已经来了。
You wanna wait for Alex? That arselicker's probably already here.
顺便说一句，你看起来像狗屎。
You look like shit, by the way. Tremendous.
美丽的
Beautiful.
好啊是 啊
OK? Yeah.
你只要告诉他。完成它。
You just have to tell him. Get it done.
是 啊
Yeah.
今晚开始，好吧。只是…别忘了装备。
It's on tonight, all right. Just... don't forget the gear.
你永远不知道你会撞上谁，比利。
You never know who you're gonna bump into, Billy.
你欠你一个人情的老朋友。
Some old mate you owe a favour to.
听着，这家伙不一样，他是波兰人或其他什么人，
Look, this bloke's different, he's Polish or something,
但我们需要他。他是有联系的，他知道什么是什么。
But we need him. He's connected and he knows what's what.
所以别用你的监狱魅力，好吗？
So just don't use your prison charm, OK?
这就是我所要求的，伙计，只是简单易行。
That's all I'm asking, mate, just nice and easy.
先生们。亚历克斯。
Gentlemen. Alex.
你好吗，伙计？我很好。你
How are you, mate? I'm good. You?
那个讨厌的人道歉了。很高兴认识你。
The annoying one's apologised. Nice to meet you.
那么，我们是上楼还是。。。？实际上，杰克想。
So, are are we going upstairs or...? Actually, Jake thought.
那么，我们是上楼还是。。。？实际上，杰克想
So, are are we going upstairs or...? Actually, Jake thought
你可能想在圆石湾见他。
you might like to meet him down at Pebble Cove.
所以他希望你们选一辆车来开。
So he would like you guys to pick a car to drive.
任何你喜欢的人。你在开玩笑吗？
Anyone you like. You're kidding?
钥匙都在里面。卫星导航按照风景路线进行编程。
Keys are all in 'em. SatNavs are programmed with the scenic route.
旅行时间约为90分钟，
Travel time's about 90 minutes,
但杰克希望你把它当成一场比赛。
but Jake would like you to think of it as a race.
杰克，杰克，杰克！你要去哪里？
Jakey, Jakey, Jakey! Where are you going?
迈克，我是山姆。嘿，山姆。
Mike, I'm Sam. Hey, Sam.
汽车！你走开，那东西是我的。
Cars! You keep away, that thing's mine.
你走开。
You keep away.
那么，你最近有没有赶上Jakemuch。
So, have you caught up with Jake much lately.
哦，不多。我…我一直在旅行。
Oh, not much. I've... I've been travelling.
几次图书之旅等等。是的。
A coupla book tours and such. Yeah.
是的，生活变得忙碌了，是吗？是的，确实如此。
Yeah, life gets busy, eh? Yeah, it does.
迈克，恐怕我得开车送你。
Mike, I'm afraid, I'm gonna have to drive you.
你在开玩笑吗？这是他妈的一口！
You're kidding me? It was a fucking sip!
啊！
Ahh!
我们要拿那个。不错的选择。
We're taking that one. Nice choice.
有人会说走吗？
Is anyone gonna say go?
“向右拐。”
"Turn right."
嘿你还好吗？
Hey. You good?
“是的，兄弟。你们都好吗？”
"Yeah, brother. How you all doing?"
你今晚要收听吗？“就在演出时间。
You gonna tune in tonight? "Right on showtime.
听着，杰克，你真的确定你想这样下去吗，伙计？"
Look, Jake, are you really sure you want it to go down this way, man?"
需要有催化剂。
There needs to be a catalyst.
我们已经好几年没有坦诚交谈了。
We haven't had an honest conversation in years.
我也没时间等了
And I don't have time to wait around
让这些人能够安心地告诉我真相。
for these guys to get comfortable enough to tell me the truth.
“是的…我明白了，兄弟。”
"Yeah... I get it, brother."
期待很快与您见面。“是的，再见。”
See you soon. "Yeah, see you."
操我，伙计！
Fuck me, mate!
一切都好吗？一辆超级跑车带着一只软公鸡为司机比赛。
Everything OK? Super car race with a soft cock for a chauffeur.
一切都很美好！
Everything's peachy!
是的，所有的规格都说我们有最快的车。
Yeah, all the specs say we have the fastest car.
嗯。它有一个赛车引擎。
Mm-hm. It's got a race engine.
你正在比赛。
You're in a race.
也许把你他妈的脚放下来！
Maybe put your fucking foot down!
如果你想做饭，冰箱里有新鲜的食物。
There are fresh ingredients in the fridge if you wanna cook.
烤牡蛎所需的一切
Everything you need for grilled oysters
在烤肉旁边的冰箱里。太好了。佩内洛普在吗？
is in the fridge by the barbecue. Great. Is Penelope here?
是的，她在楼下，先生。
Yes, she is. Downstairs, sir.
客人将分乘三辆车抵达。
The guests are gonna be arriving in three separate cars.
在车库和他们见面，带他们到后台的房间。
Meet them in the garage, take them to their rooms down the backstairs.
没问题。之后，你们可以休息一晚。
No problem. After that, you guys can take the night off.
只打开闸门密码。
Put the gate on code only.
你好，杰克先生。一切都好吗？一切都准备好了吗，先生？太棒了
Hello, Mr Jake. Everything good? Everything in place, sir? Great.
我想我今晚可能会做饭。杰克先生，你确定要这么做吗？
I think I might cook tonight. You sure you wanna do that, Mr Jake?
我尽量不把事情搞得一团糟。
I'll try not to make a mess.
“你好。”谢谢他妈的！你收到我的留言了吗？
"Hello." Thank fuck! Did you get my message?
今晚不要去房子。计划改变了。
Don't go to the house tonight. The plan has changed.
“我没有改变计划。一切都安排好了。”
"I'm not changing plans. Everything's been organised."
不，不，你必须改变计划。我以为房子会空的。
No, no, you have to change the plan. I thought the house would be empty.
他会在那里。“一切都在进行。
He'll be there. "It's going ahead.
是时候偿还债务了。“不，今晚不能进行了！
Time to clear your debt." No, it can't go ahead tonight!
你听见了吗？他会在那里！
You hear me? He'll be there!
我会去的。太近了！他会知道的。
I'll be there. It's too close! He'll know.
拜托，伙计，他妈的走开！
Please, man, just back the fuck off!
TMD！TMD！
Fuck! Fuck!
玩得开心吗，福利先生？
Having fun, Mr Foley?
佩内洛普。
Penelope.
山姆告诉你发生了什么事吗？只不过这是个大赌注。
Did Sam tell you what's going on? Only that it's big stakes.
山姆告诉你发生了什么事吗？只是这是个大赌注
Did Sam tell you what's going on? Only that it's big stakes
我可能会早点完成。他没有详细说明。
and that I'll probably finish early. He didn't elaborate.
RFID芯片。活的法定货币。
RFID chips. Live and legal tender.
现金
Cash.
五个相等的堆栈，德州扑克。
Five equal stacks, Texas Hold'em.
是的，老板。
Yes, boss.
是的，当然。
Yes, of course.
嘿，听着…我得走了。
Hey, look... I gotta go.
再见爱你。
Bye. Love you.
麦克！走吧！
Mikey! Let's go!
你没事吧？是的。
You all right? Yep.
让我们开始吧。
Let's hit it.
他来了，亚历克斯。
There he is. Alex.
很高兴见到你，杰克。嗨。
Good to see you, Jake. Hiya.
保罗。杰基小子。总是一种乐趣。
Paul. Jakey boy. Always a pleasure.
迈克。杰克。看看这个！
Mike. Jake. Look at this!
好啊
OK?
好吗，福利先生？一切都好，克里斯。明天见。
All good, Mr Foley? All good, Chris. See you tomorrow.
你知道亨施克附近还有其他葡萄酒。
You do know there are other wines beside Henschke.
是的，我对葡萄酒有个规矩，除非你要喝，否则不要买。
Yeah, I have a rule with wine, don't buy it unless you're gonna drink it.
我知道你会这么说，这么小的葡萄园，
I knew you would say something like that, so small vineyard,
迈凯轮谷西拉。美好的天鹅绒手套。
McLaren Vale shiraz. Nice. A velvet glove.
嗯，致敬。时间太长了。
Hmm. Salute. It's been too long.
干杯，伙计们。敬德鲁和你杰克。
Cheers, lads. To Drew and to you Jake.
缺席的朋友。
Absent friends.
德鲁怎么样？好的
How is Drew? Good.
嗯！车怎么样？
Mmm! How were the cars?
哦，那辆迈巴赫太棒了！我放下脚来了。
Oh, that Maybach is amazing! I put my foot down and I was here.
是的，我不知道我该怎么开车，
Yeah, I wouldn't know how mine was to drive,
因为你把他妈的有趣的警察派过去了。
cos you sent the fucking fun police over there.
我很高兴你喜欢这些车，因为它们是你的。
Well, I'm glad you liked the cars, because they're yours.
我的礼物。什么
My gift. What?
我的意思是，迈巴赫是一辆价值百万美元的汽车，杰克。
I mean, that Maybach is a million-dollar car, Jake.
原谅我的愤世嫉俗，但有什么问题？没有什么可抓的。
Forgive my cynicism, but what's the catch? There's no catch.
我只是想今晚我们会玩得开心一点，赌一把。
I just thought we'd have a bit of fun and up the stakes tonight.
汽车是你的，所有权是你的，
The cars are yours, titles signed over to you,
或者…你可以放弃梦想中的汽车
or... you can give up the dream car
并交换它，
and exchange it,
每个500万美元的筹码。
For $5 million in chips each.
天哪$500万？梭哈
Holy shit! $5 million? Texas Hold'em.
赢家通吃。
Winner take all.
有几条皱纹。第一，你必须玩，你不能坐在外面。
There's a couple of wrinkles. One, you have to play, you can't sit out.
第二，如果你们中有一个人想保留这辆车，那就是这样。
Two, if one of you wants to keep the car, then that's that.
这是一进，全进，我们就按平常的赌注打球。
It's one in, all in, and we'll just play for our usual stakes.
TMD！哪辆车先来？迈巴赫。
Fuck! Which car came first? The Maybach.
亚历克斯，这让你按捺不住了。你只需要做决定。
That puts you on the button, Alex. You just gotta make the decision.
你想要这辆车，还是要薯条？
Do you want the car, or do you want the chips?
我让你来讨论。山姆，能回答你的问题吗？
I'll leave you to discuss it. Sam, can answer your questions?
记住，如果你真的玩
Just remember, if you do play
你必须接受结果。
you have to accept the outcome.
如果你不玩
If you don't play
你也必须接受这个结果。
You have to accept that outcome too.
等等。在我们开始之前，
W-Wait. Before we start,
我们不能这样做。不能做什么？
We can't do this. Can't do what?
我们不能坐车。你说得对，我们不能开车。
We can't take the cars. You're damn right we can't take the cars.
这是五百万的筹码。扑克之夜，我们他妈的走吧！
It's five million in chips. It's poker night, let's fucking go!
我们不能拿走汽车或芯片。
We can't take the cars or the chips.
这太疯狂了！
This is crazy!
我的意思是，让我们玩我们的正常赌注，嗯？
I mean, let's just play for our normal stakes, eh?
我不想觉得我欠杰克什么。
I don't wanna feel like I owe Jake anything.
这是每个500万的筹码。
This is five million in chips each.
对吧，山姆？嗯。
Right, Sam? Mm-hm.
那会是什么，先生们？
So, what's it gonna be, gents?
2500万。
25 million on the table.
这些人是谁？和我一起长大的人。
Who are these guys? The guys I grew up with.
我要给ema一些重要的经历，
I'm giving 'em a couple of the big experiences,
看在过去的份上和他们的头做爱。
and fucking with their heads for old times' sake.
他们可能会说蠢话。当他们喝酒的时候，好吗？
They will probably say stupid shit. When they drink, OK?
如果他们认为自己有一半的机会，他们会和床头柜调情。
And they'll flirt with the bedposts if they think they've half a chance.
米奇，等等。只是
Mikey, wait. Just...
这太过分了。
This is too much.
你知道，我很好，我不需要这个。
You know, I'm doing OK, I don't need this.
我为你感到高兴，亚历克斯，你做得很好，
I'm happy for you, Alex, that you're doing OK,
你的书在卖，太好了。
that your books are selling, that's great.
我做得不好。
I'm not doing OK.
我想玩。
And I wanna play.
只要答应，亚历克斯。好的
Just say yes, Alex. Fine.
你呢，保罗？
What about you, Paul?
我想我们应该…说是的，亚历克斯。
I think we should... just say yes, Alex.
嗯。
Mm-hm.
他们在里面。好的
They're in. Good.
我们正在这样做。是的，我们正在这样做。
We're doing this. Yeah, we're doing this.
你做事不能半途而废，杰克·切尔斯。干杯
You don't do things by halves, Jake. Cheers. Cheers.
这只是一场比赛，亚历克斯。
It's just a game, Alex.
这是一个美丽的水滴。
This is a beautiful drop.
天哪！操我！
Sweet Jesus! Fuck me!
不是说我不喜欢这酒，杰克，它他妈的很可爱，
Not that I don't appreciate the wine, Jake, it's fucking lovely,
但我要给我自己的扑克玩家拿杯饮料。
but I'll grab myself a poker player's drink.
拿着瓶子。干杯
Take the bottle. Cheers.
我们走吧，嗯？
Let's go, eh?
如果你愿意的话，那边有个雪茄盒。我不介意。
There's a humidor over there if you like. Don't mind if I do.
你好我是迈克尔。我是佩内洛普。
Hello. I'm Michael. I'm Penelope.
你是左手还是右手？我是对的。
Are you left or right-handed? I'm right.
你会没事的。
You'll be fine.
晚上好，先生们。我是今晚的经销商。
Good evening, gentlemen. I'm your dealer for tonight.
我叫佩内洛普。你好，佩内洛普，我是保罗。
My name is Penelope. Hello, Penelope, I'm Paul.
你好，保罗。亚历克斯。亚历克斯。
Hi, Paul. Alex. Alex.
在我的右手边，迈克尔。
On my right hand here, Michael.
这是一笔500万美元的投资。没有反驳。梭哈
It's a five million buy in. No rebuys. Texas Hold'em.
赢家通吃。我们将在25000美元启动小型盲板，
Winner takes all. We will start the small blind at 25,000,
50000英镑的大盲人。
the big blind at 50,000.
祝大家好运。
Good luck to you all.
那么，如果你如此热爱艺术，那你为什么要偷它呢？
So, if you love art so much, then why do you steal it?
拥有它。
To possess it.
即使只是短暂的，为了靠近到能闻到帆布的味道，
Even just briefly, to be close enough to smell the canvas,
为了触摸笔触，
to touch the brush strokes,
拥有它。
To have possessed it.
也许是有点太钝了
Maybe it's just a bit too obtuse
比利，深深地爱着你。
and deep for you, Billy.
也许你只是不够聪明，无法理解。
Maybe you're just not smart enough to understand.
我很聪明知道你脸上的哪一部分
I'm smart enough to know which part of your face
会流血最多的。
Is gonna bleed the most.
该死的雪貂！
Fucking ferret!
目标来了。
Here comes the target.
呼叫呼叫
Call. Call.
举起…175。
Raise... 175.
筹集175000美元。
Raise 175,000.
出来亚历克斯出去了。
Out. Alex is out.
呼叫呼叫
Call. Call.
检查检查
Check. Check.
检查赌，赌10万。
Check. Bet. Bet 100,000.
升起400。升起400。
Raise 400. Raise 400.
呼叫
Call.
山姆出去了。
Sam's out.
检查检查
Check. Check.
700,000.
迈克尔？
Michael?
筹集两百万。筹集两百万。
Raise two million. Raise two million.
保罗出去了。
Paul is out.
全部投入。杰克全力以赴。
All in. Jake goes all in.
迈克尔？
Michael?
快速游戏是一个好游戏，嗯，杰克？
A quick game is a good game, eh, Jake?
谢谢你的邀请。我打电话。全部投入。
Thanks for the invite. I call. All in.
他妈的第一手。
First fucking hand.
一千万在锅里。
Ten million in the pot.
哦哦，你们都有同样的牌。
Oh! Oh, you both have the same cards.
杰克和十。迈克尔有红心，杰克有钻石。
Jack and ten. Michael has hearts, Jake has diamonds.
我们两人都有平局或可能平局。
We have a straight or a possible flush draw on both.
开锅，先生们。
Split pot, gentlemen.
就在中间。
Right down the middle.
直接从中间往下走。
Straight down the middle.
谈到你从墨尔本步行到悉尼，
Talking about you walking from Melbourne to Sydney,
大约25年了。
For about 25 fucking years.
而我从未想过的故事，
And the bit of the story I've never figured out,
你没有真正完成旅程？哦，是的。
you didn't actually complete the journey? Oh, I did, yeah.
我做到了。我做到了。
I did. I did.
在车里。开始讲这个故事
In a car. Start telling that story
将来你从墨尔本到悉尼的散步，
in the future about the walk you did from Melbourne to Sydney,
讲述从墨尔本到奥博斯特的步行故事。这是正确的。
Tell the story about the walk from Melbourne to Orbost. That's right.
这是虚假广告，伙计。
It is false advertising, mate.
这是一个很大的标题，但故事没有达到标题。
It's a big title, and the story doesn't live up to the title.
绝对虚假的广告。有点像你的上一本书。
Absolutely false advertising. A bit like your last book.
然后他开始给我冰毒…香烟。
And then he proceeded to offer me this... cigarette.
你喝了吗？我做到了。我认为不这样做是不礼貌的。
Did you imbibe? I did. I thought it would be rude not to.
所以，不管怎样，我觉得没有什么特别的不同，
So, anyway, I don't feel particularly different,
直到那天晚上晚些时候，我爬上楼梯去餐馆，
until later that night, I went upstairs to the restaurant,
我在看这支乐队，然后转过身来
and I'm watching this band, and then I turn around
看着窗外，我回来了，那里是厨房。
And look out the window, and I came back and there's the kitchen.
乐队他妈的消失了！
The band's fucking disappeared!
所以我又往窗外看，乐队又来了。
So I look out the window again, there's the band again.
我他妈的一直在倒下，
And I'm fucking falling over all the time going,
“我一定是真的疯了。”
"I must be really out of my mind here."
我花了大约一个小时才意识到
It took me about an hour to realise
那是一家旋转屋顶餐厅。
That it was a revolving rooftop restaurant.
你他妈的白痴！我知道。太棒了！
You fucking idiot! I know. That's brilliant!
这是我从政的开始。
And that was my start in politics.
哦，滚开！
Oh, fuck off!
福莱先生在我的储物柜里给了我一份礼物。
Mr Foley left me a gift in my locker.
不，我回家后会给你看。
No, I'm gonna show you when I get home.
我们可以去你想去的任何地方。听着，我很兴奋。
We can go anywhere you want. Look, I'm excited.
你必须看到它才能相信它。听着，我现在在回家的路上，
You've gotta see it to believe it. Look, I'm on my way home now,
我很快就会见到你。
I'll see you soon.
怎么了，伙计？！
What's going on, man?!
我们到了拉斯维加斯，我们到了酒店房间，
We get to Vegas, we get to the hotel rooms,
所以我开始看…屁股问题。
so I start go ogling... arse problems.
小心小心我的屁股有危险！
Caution! Caution! My arse is in danger!
正确的每次你收缩括约肌，
Right. Every time you flinch your sphincter,
这就像是电击穿了我的身体。
it was like an electric shock through my body.
我们找到这位专家，我躺下了，亚历克斯和我在一起。
We get to this specialist, and I lay down, and Alex is there with me.
谢谢你，亚历克斯。我躺下，
Thank you, Alex. And I lay down,
他看了一下。他说：“哦，是的！”
And he has a look at it. He's like, "Oh, yep!"
“是的，你得了肛周脓肿。”哦！
"Yeah, you've got a perianal abscess." Ohh!
在拉斯维加斯度过了一个很棒的周末，不是吗，亚历克斯？
It was a terrific weekend in Vegas, wasn't it, Alex?
“嘿，贝克。”
"Hey, Bec."
你打算什么时候告诉我？
When were you going to tell me?
呃，嘿，我在开车，
Er, hey, I'm driving,
这是一些相当大的东西。
this is some pretty big stuff.
让我靠边停车，我们就可以正常交谈了。
Just let me pull over and we can talk properly.
我是个孩子，是吗？我无法面对现实或其他什么？
I'm a kid, is that it? I can't handle reality or something?
“为什么让我一直呆在黑暗中？”
"What's the reason for keeping me in that dark?"
听着，孩子。。。
Listen, kiddo...
听着，孩子
Listen, kiddo
大约五个月前。。。
about five months ago...
这真的很难。
This is really hard.
你爸爸做了输精管切除术。好啊
Your dad had a vasectomy. OK?
“他没有……他只是做了，他没有和我讨论。”
"He didn't... He just did it, he didn't discuss it with me."
现在我一直知道你爸爸，他。。。
Now I've always known that your dad, he...
现在我一直知道你爸爸，他
Now I've always known that your dad, he
他很爱你。他不想让你的生活复杂化
he loves you so much. And he didn't wanna complicate your life
“你年轻的时候有一个同父异母的兄弟姐妹。”
"With a half-sibling when you were younger."
但我一直认为
But I always thought that
我们最终会有机会生孩子。
we would eventually get the chance to have a baby.
输精管结扎术新闻
So the vasectomy news
那是，呃
that was, er
我去过他的办公室
I've been in his office
看看他的病历。
looking at his medical records.
他于9月被确诊。
He was diagnosed in September.
他于9月确诊
He was diagnosed in September
患有胰腺癌。
with pancreatic cancer.
“他要死了！
"He's dying!
他快死了！"
He's dying!"
他不会告诉我的！
He wasn't going to tell me!
没关系，Bec，
It's OK, Bec,
我会来接你的，好吗？"
I'm gonna come and get you, OK?"
呆在原地，好吗？没事的，亲爱的，我来了。
Just stay where you are, OK? It's OK, honey, I'm coming.
我会来接你然后
I'm gonna come and get you and then
我们一起去和你爸爸谈谈，好吗？
we'll both go and talk to your dad together, OK?
500.
嘿，山姆，去帮我看看。
Hey, Sam, go and check that out for me.
门可能没有关上，它正在激活系统。
The door might not be closed, it's activating the system.
是的，没问题。
Yeah, no problem.
只有两对。实际上没有八个。
Just two pair. Didn't actually have the eight.
再一次
Again!
看看这个家伙。
Look at this guy.
我希望他是个更好的律师。
I hope he's a better lawyer.
我希望他是个更好的律师
I hope he's a better lawyer
比他是一个纸牌玩家。我也是。
than he is a card player. So do I.
呼叫
Call.
你们这些混蛋有人要对付我吗？画！
Anyone of you motherfuckers gonna deal me in? Drew!
画！嘿，德鲁！
Drew! Hey, Drew!
怎么了，兄弟？你好吗？
What's up, brother? How you doing?
怎么了，兄弟？
What's up, brother?
给那个人喝一杯。你在吃什么，德鲁？
Get the man a drink. What are you having, Drew?
冰龙舌兰酒，菠萝片。
Tequila on ice, slice of pineapple.
好吧。他喜欢他的水果。
Alrighty. He likes his fruit.
嘿有些事我需要告诉你。
Hey. Some things I need to catch you up on.
是的，我看到了大笔资金的流动。
Yeah, I'm seeing the big money move.
我知道我说过我不会来的，但是。。。
I know I said I wasn't gonna make it, but...
我们会继续玩吗？不，我不这么认为。
Are we gonna keep playing? No, I don't think so.
她要去哪里？我们还在玩，不是吗？
Where's she going? We're still playing, aren't we?
操我！
Fuck me!
杰克让我这个星期把里弗利恩交给你们。
Jake asked me to turn RIFFLE on to you guys this week.
你为什么要把军事级别的监视程序交给我们？
Why would you turn a military grade surveillance program me on us?
起初只是为了笑，
At first it was just for laughs,
也许会抓到你在车道上抓球，
maybe catch you scratching your balls in your driveway,
在扑克之夜展示。但里弗利并没有停止，
show it on poker night. But RIFFLE doesn't stop,
它在你的手机、家庭安全、电脑上交错。
it crisscrosses your cell phones, home security, computers.
我不是说我们什么都知道，
Now, I'm not saying we know everything,
但我们知道的足够让我上他妈的飞机。
but we know enough to get me on a motherfucking plane.
我觉得恶心！
I feel sick!
我并不惊讶，亚历克斯。我毒死了你。
I'm not surprised, Alex. I poisoned you.
在你的烤杯底座上。
On the base of your toasting glasses.
它会沾在你的手上…你的脸上。
It would have got on your hands... your faces.
现在它在你的血液中。
And now it's in your bloodstream.
这不好笑。
That's not funny.
你是认真的吗？！
Are you serious?!
毒死？滚开，他在开玩笑。
Poisoned? Fuck off, he's joking.
他是吗？
Is he?
我像个混蛋一样大汗淋漓。
I'm sweating like a motherfucker.
我感觉不太好。最初的迹象是出汗
I don't feel too good. First signs are sweating
失去平衡，恶心，然后…然后呢？
Loss of balance, nausea, and then... Then what?
别胡闹了。
Stop fucking around.
你想让我们死吗？
You want us dead?
我被诊断出患有可手术的胰腺癌。
I've been diagnosed with an inoperable pancreatic cancer.
这是死刑判决。
It's a death sentence.
所以现在我们都处于同一水平。
So now we're all on the same level.
触摸板。把他带过来。
Touch pad. Bring him over.
美丽的
Beautiful.
你为我做了这件事。天哪！TMD！
You've done the job for me. Jesus! Fuck!
他妈的，米奇？你打算怎么做，开枪打死我们？射杀杰克？我
What the fuck, Mikey? What was you gonna do, shoot us? Shoot Jake? Me.
我要开枪打死我。
I was gonna shoot me.
这就是计划。
That was the plan.
我要跟你们说再见然后…开枪自杀。
I was gonna say goodbye to you all and... shoot myself.
这是关于生意的吗？你认为我们会让你淹死吗？
Is this about the business? You think, we was gonna let you drown?
你为什么不伸出援手？是 啊我不知道你这么不开心。
Why didn't you reach out? Yeah. I had no idea you were this unhappy.
我每天放两瓶伏特加，亚历克斯。
I put back two bottles of vodka a day, Alex.
这不是一个快乐的人的习惯。
That's not the habit of a happy person.
我对死亡很满意。
I'm all right with death.
我不是！
I'm not!
我有妻子和孩子。我有依赖我的人。
I have a wife and kids. I've got people who depend on me.
代码是什么？
What is the code?
我不能告诉你。代码是什么？
I can't tell you. What's the code?
你想要另一个吗？他妈的代码是什么？
You want another one? What is the fucking code?
汽车车，车！
Car! Car, car!
把货车开走！来吧
Get rid of the van! Come on.
我说下来！使沮丧
I said get down! Get down!
嘿…没有声音，你听见了吗？
Hey... no noise, you hear me?
对，当汽车通过时，
Right, when the car goes through,
跳到大门前阻止他们关门。
Jumped in front of the gates, stop 'em from closing.
什么
What?
它不是那样工作的，它一直在继续。
It doesn't work that way, it keeps going.
-大门会压坏汽车。-是这样吗？谢谢
- The gate can crush the car. - Is that right? Thanks.
你有很多银行账户，保罗。储蓄、支票、，
You got a bunch of bank accounts, Paul. Savings, checking,
全部为零。照顾你的家人怎么样？
all on zero. How's that taking care of your family?
我被勒索了。
I'm being blackmailed.
他们有我和一个女孩的视频。如果它出来了，我是
They've got video of me with a girl. If it comes out, I'm
我把我所有的钱都给了他们，他们想要的比我更多。
I gave them all the money I have, they want more than I have.
告诉我密码。
Tell me the code.
告诉我编码员你会被压垮的！
Tell me the code or you're gonna get crushed!
伙计们，他妈的快点。告诉我密码，否则你会被压死的。
Fucking hurry up, mates. Tell me the code or you're gonna get crushed.
氧指数！密码你马上就会变成水坑。密码
Oi! Code. You're gonna turn into a puddle in a minute. Code.
告诉他！
Tell him!
1967!
我以为我们只是来偷东西，现在我们是杀人犯了？
I thought we were just here to steal, we are murderers now?
你最多只会遭到狂轰滥炸。
You'll only get manslaughter at most.
在你不能再给孩子钱之后，你做了什么？
And after you couldn't give the dude no more money, what did you do?
你给他们什么，保罗？
What did you give 'em, Paul?
满意的。
Jake.
电子邮件地址、电话号码
Email addresses, phone numbers
敏感信息。
sensitive information.
我只是想争取时间。我保证，杰克。对不起，伙计。
I was just trying to buy time. I promise, Jake. I'm sorry, man.
谁在勒索你？
Who's blackmailing you?
胜利者。你哥哥？！
Victor. Your brother?!
是的，我哥哥。
Yeah, my brother.
我真他妈的很羞愧！
I'm just so fucking ashamed!
哦，操！这是怎么一回事？
Oh, fuck! What is it?
我有外遇。
I'm having an affair.
一个非常不准确的词。
A terribly inexact word.
不充分的
Insufficient.
我从来没有故意背叛任何人的意图。
It was never my intention to deliberately betray anyone.
杰克，发生在我身上的是我坠入爱河。
What happened to me, Jake, is that I fell in love.
碰巧我爱上了你结婚的女人。
It just so happens I fell in love with the woman you're married to.
我不能死。
I can't die.
我们要生孩子了。
We're having a baby.
我不能死。
I can't die.
你不会死的。
You're not gonna fucking die.
反正今晚不行。
Not tonight, anyway.
我只是用了几滴，远远不够杀死你。
I just used a couple of drops, nowhere near enough to kill you.
只够把你搞砸，让你思考。
Just enough to fuck you up and get you thinking.
它很快就会磨损。
It'll wear off soon.
我只是想让你感觉一下我在哪里。
I just wanted you for a moment to feel where I am.
通过我的眼睛看事物。
To see things through my eyes.
我的小女儿要被火车撞了。
My little girl is about to be hit by a train.
我对此无能为力。。。
And there's nothing I can do about it...
我无能为力
And there's nothing I can do about it
因为我是火车。
cos I am the train.
那你还有多久，伙计？
So how long have you got, man?
足够长的时间来完成比赛？
Long enough to finish the game?
TMD！
Fuck!
律师建议信托基金，这样他们就可以继续收取年费。
Lawyers recommend trust funds so they can keep charging annual fees.
事实上，在大多数情况下，只是简单地转账
In fact, in most instances, simply transferring money
是任何正常银行账户的免税礼品。
is a tax-free gift to any normal bank account.
这是更好的选择。
That's the better option.
你们他妈的不明白。
You fucking guys don't get it.
杰克和我把你带到了公司的底层。
Jake and I brought you into the company at the ground level.
米奇，你一周内卖掉了你的股票。亚历克斯用他的劳力士换了一辆劳力士。
Mikey, you sold your shares in a week. Alex traded his for a Rolex.
保罗坐头等舱去拉斯维加斯。
And Paul goes to Vegas first class.
现在，如果由我决定，
Now, if it was up to me,
我会把我们留给你的一切都给你。
I would have given you all that we put aside for you.
我告诉他，“冷静点，让我们从一半开始。”
And I told him, "Chill the fuck out, let's just start them with half."
因为我们认识你们这些混蛋。
Because we know you motherfuckers.
什么意思？我们还有股份吗？是 啊
What do you mean? We've still got shares? Yeah.
多少钱？
How much?
2500万美元的扑克筹码。
$25 million in poker chips.
去他妈的！
Get fucked!
呃，杰克？
Erm, Jake?
卧槽？
What the fuck?
我希望这不是你的另一个惊喜，杰克？不
I hope this isn't another one of your surprises, Jake? No.
我是维克多。他来这里是为了艺术。
It's Victor. He's here for the art.
啊，操！
Ah, fuck!
当你说当时的家庭充满了澳大利亚艺术，
When you said then house was full of Australian art,
你是指这样的碎片吗？他们不知道我们在哪里，
did you mean pieces like this? They don't know where we are,
在他们找到楼梯之前我们滚吧。穿过地窖。
Let's fuck off before they find the stairs. Through the cellar.
土著艺术不是我的专长。
Aboriginal art is not my forte.
它们值什么吗？嗯，是的，其中一些是。
Are they worth anything? Well, yes, some of them are.
很贵，但…这件艺术品的市场
Very expensive, but... the market for this art
吸引特定类型的买家
attracts a certain type of buyer
他在精神层面上与我联系。
who connects with it on a spiritual plane.
这是一座大房子，给我们找点能卖的。
It's a big house, find us something we can sell.
你认为这个地方是空的吗？
Do you think the place is empty?
三辆车进来了，四辆出来了，都是不同的车。
Three cars came in, four came out, all different cars.
嘘！别他妈的嘘我！
Shush! Don't fucking shush me!
他们有枪。
They have guns.
别担心。
Don't worry about that.
沃霍尔。
Warhol.
他很有名，对吧？太出名了。
Well, he's famous, right? Too famous.
这是一张星期日B晨报。
It's a Sunday B Morning print.
如果那样的话，就有几家大型零售店。
A couple of grand retail if that.
不适合我们。
Not for us.
不错。
Not bad.
亨利·詹姆斯·约翰·斯通。
Henry James John stone.
在这种情况下很难找到。
Hard to find in this condition.
看看他画灯的方式。
Look at the way he painted the light.
他来到澳大利亚金矿，
He came to Australia to mine for gold,
讽刺的是，他成了一名摄影师。
ironically, became a photographer.
有价值的隐马尔可夫模型。
Valuable? Hmm.
我们可能会卖掉它们。
We could probably sell them.
不过，这不会是一张大票。
It wouldn't be a big ticket, though.
氧指数！
Oi!
楼梯在这里。
Stairs down here.
嘘！
Shh!
“好吧，我们开始吧。”
"All right, here we go."
你想喝一杯吗？
You want a drink?
有人已经有了。
Somebody already has.
哦
Oh.
看看这个！美好的
Look at this! Nice!
这是他妈的地下两层。繁荣
And this is a fucking two storeys underground. Boom!
没人在家。是的，有。
Nobody's home. Yes, there is.
这支雪茄没有点燃。
This cigar didn't light itself.
这里有很多吸引眼球的东西。
There's a lot of eye candy in here.
他们躲在某处。
They're hiding somewhere.
比利，四处看看。
Billy, check around.
好的，我们有枪，让我们阻止这些混蛋。我没有枪。
OK, we got the guns, let's stop these fuckers. I don't have guns.
你有恐慌室，没有枪械？
You got a panic room, no firearms?
我有一个急救室，我不需要枪支。
I've got a panic room so I don't need firearms.
维克多，他们很可能刚刚搞砸了。看看周围！
Victor, they probably just fucked off. Look around!
好啊
OK.
胜利者。维克多，看看这个房间，伙计！
Victor. Victor, look at this room, man!
顶级美元！这就像阿里巴巴的洞穴，伙计！
Top dollar! It's like Ali Baba's cave, man!
我在看什么？1889.墨尔本。
What am I looking at? 1889. Melbourne.
9x5印象展。
9x5 Impression exhibition.
182件作品主要绘在雪茄盒盖上。
182 works painted mainly on cigar box lids.
他们每人卖一几内亚，几美元。
They sold for a guinea each, a couple of bucks.
汤姆·罗伯茨，亚瑟街，查尔斯·康德。
Tom Roberts, Arthur Street on, Charles Conder.
你成功了！
You've hit the trifecta!
现在你看到的是300万美元的拍卖，很简单。
Now you are looking at three million at auction, easy.
灰色市场对我们来说，高达六位数。
Grey market to us, high six figures.
快乐的日子！
Happy days!
我知道你还在这里，杰克。
I know you're still here, Jake.
哈是的，你他妈的是，不是吗！
Ha! Yes, you fucking are, aren't you!
你好，杰克。已经有一段时间了。
Hello, Jake. It's been a while.
你不想和一个老朋友打招呼吗？
Aren't you gonna say hey to an old mate?
我们不会伤害任何人，我们只会接受艺术。
We ain't gonna hurt anyone, we're just gonna take the art.
问部长为什么不报警比较安全。
Ask the Minister why it's safer not to call the cops.
我们他妈的为什么上电视？
Why the fuck are we on TV?
因为我们的主人还在房子里。
Because our host is still somewhere in the house.
检查那些楼梯。
Check up those stairs.
这里还有什么？
What else is in here?
我们正要在黑暗中袭击这个地方。
We were just gonna hit this place in darkness.
没什么私事。然后保罗说。
Nothing personal. Then Paul said.
没什么私事。然后保罗说
Nothing personal. Then Paul said
你本来要来的，我想，“去他妈的！
you were gonna be here and I thought, "Fuck it!
我想把它变成个人的！"
I wanna make it personal!"
恐慌室？你不能用它射死他妈的。
A panic room? You can't shoot a motherfucker with it.
我们有迈克的枪。它只有一颗子弹。
We've got Mike's gun. It's only got one bullet.
我打算自杀，你只需要一颗子弹。
I was planning on killing myself, you only need one bullet for that.
克拉丽斯·贝克特。天才
Clarice Beckett. Genius!
我们可以在心跳中移动这些。
We can move these in a heartbeat.
另一条街上。
Another Street on.
威廉·杜贝尔。餐厅里的女人。
William Do bell. Woman In Restaurant.
上次售价935000！
Last sold for 935,000!
约翰·彼得·罗素！太罕见了！他几乎从未展出过。
John Peter Russell! So rare! He had hardly ever exhibited.
劳崔克和梵高的同学。
Classmate of Lautrec and Van Gogh.
妻子去世后，他悲痛地销毁了400件杰作。
He destroyed 400 of his masterworks in grief when his wife died.
这是真他妈的钱！多少钱？
This is real fucking money! How much?
即使在廉价地下室，我们也在走开
Even at bargain basement, we are walking away
有几百万。
With a couple of million.
你听到了吗，杰克？
You hear that, Jake?
我们知道你在这里有什么！
We know what you've got here!
氧指数。楼梯通向厨房。我在那里没看到任何人。
Oi. The stairs lead to the kitchen. I didn't see anyone there.
就像我在外面或车库里没见过任何人一样。
Just like I haven't seen anyone out here or in the garage.
你知道那是什么吗，维克多？因为这里没有人。
And you know what that is, Victor? Cos there's no one fucking here.
帮助冥河。
Help Styx.
走吧！
Let's go!
杰克，我们六个人三个人，我们可以带走他们。
Jake, there's six of us and three of them, we can take 'em.
这只是他妈的维克多。
It's only fucking Victor.
他们有三支猎枪和一颗子弹。
They've got three shotguns against one bullet.
让我们呆在这里直到他离开，好吗？
Let's just stay down here until he fucks off, OK?
他肾上腺素化程度越高，药物的作用就越大。
The more adrenalized he gets, the harder that drug's gonna hit.
那么，这值多少钱？可能有几百K。
So, what's this worth? A couple of hundred K maybe.
他在街上画了很多。即使是一幅不那么重要的作品，
He painted a lot Street on. Even with a less significant work,
他留下了天才的印记。看
he leaves his mark of genius. Look.
许多人认为这些是反思的标志。
A lot of people believe that these marks of reflection.
很多人相信这些反映
A lot of people believe that these marks of reflection
正在街上画一幅他自己画的肖像画。
are Street on painting a portrait of himself painting the glass.
你看到了吗？这就像一个人靠在画架上。
You see? It's like a man leaning over an easel.
所以，我们的伴侣有一个绿色的脑袋，是吗？
So, our mate had a green head, did he?
我告诉你，厨房里有一幅很好的画。
I tell ya, there's a really good painting in the kitchen.
两个男人在打牌，一个在抽烟斗，
It's a couple of men playing cards, one's smoking a pipe,
戴着有趣的帽子。这是我喜欢的绘画类型。你知道为什么吗？
wearing funny hats. That's the type of painting I like. You know why?
隐马尔可夫模型？因为它讲述了一个他妈的故事。
Hmm? Cos it tells a fucking story.
几个家伙在玩扑克，
A couple of blokes playing poker,
他们在撒尿，他们在胡说八道。
they're on the piss, they're talking shit.
我是说，那只是一个该死的高脚杯。
I mean, that's just a fucking goblet.
白色烟斗？是 啊
A white pipe? Yeah.
一顶高帽子？是的，一顶有趣的帽子。
A tall hat? Yeah, a funny hat.
TMD！
Fuck!
上帝啊她在这里干什么？
Jesus! What's she doing here?
比利！参观者。
Billy! Visitors.
这是谁，杰克？
Who's this, Jake?
计划改变了。把枪给我，里面只有一颗子弹，伙计。
Plan's changed. Give me the gun. There's only one bullet in it, man.
他们不知道。米奇，我们要按照你的计划去做。
They don't know that. Mikey, we're gonna go with your plan.
我会吓唬这个混蛋，然后把他们分开。我和你一起去。
I'll bluff this prick and I'll split 'em up. I'll come with you.
开门，迈克。
Get the door, Mike.
爸爸爸爸
Dad? Dad?
你好，女士们。噢，你好，女们！
Hello, ladies. Oh, hello, ladies!
-过来，过来-过来。
- Come on, come here. - Come here.
离开
Get off!
过来。啊！
Come here. Argh!
倒霉！
Shit!
过来！
Come here!
过来…过来你。。。
Come... Come here you...
过来！
Come here!
胜利者。胜利者。
Victor. Victor.
胜利者！厨房里的画他妈的是塞尚！
Victor! The painting in the kitchen is a fucking Cezanne!
这是一件价值2亿美元的物品！
That's a $200 million item!
我们在这里和谁打交道？
Who are we dealing with here?
像那样拥有艺术的人有很多种方法可以搞砸你。
People who own art like that have got many ways of fucking you up.
走开！
Go... away!
毕竟是我的幸运日。
My lucky day after all.
你知道，直到你出现之前，一切都很糟糕。
You know, things were looking dull as shit till you turned up.
这改变了一切，不是吗，杰克？
Well, this changes things, doesn't it, Jake?
我想你认识这些女人。
I'm assuming you know these women.
进来，你这个混蛋！
Come on in here, you prick!
-你听见了吗，杰克？-把屁股放进去！
- Do you hear me, Jake? - Get your arse in here!
他妈的，伙计？！
What the fuck, man?!
爸爸倒霉！
Dad! Shit!
这他妈的是谁？！我们的主人。
Who the fuck is this?! Our host.
杰克…操…福利！
Jake... Fucking... Foley!
看着你，大人物。你走进房间，手里拿着枪，
Lok at you, Big Shot. You come into the room, gun in your hand,
就像一个普通的罪犯。维克多，我看你还是那个该死的磁铁
like a common criminal. Victor. I see you're the same shit magnet
谁到处偷别人的东西。
Who goes around stealing other people's stuff.
别太自大，弗利，你有三把猎枪在训练你，
Don't get too cocky, Foley, you've got three shotguns trained on you,
你不可能抓住我们所有人！我只是瞄准你，维克多。
You can't get all of us! I'm only aiming at you, Victor.
好吧，我想我们是在墨西哥对峙我的朋友。
Well, I guess we're in a Mexican stand-off my friend.
你向我开枪，
You shoot me,
我可能会死，也可能不会死，这取决于你是否真的会开枪，不是吗？
I may or may not die, depends if you can shoot really, doesn't it?
即使你抓到我，这两个人还是会开枪打死你，拿走你的艺术品。
And even if you get me, these two will still shoot you, take your art.
即使你抓到我，这两个人还是会开枪打死你，拿走你的艺术
And even if you get me, these two will still shoot you, take your art
破坏这些精美的标本。不，我不会。
and damage these fine specimens. No, I won't.
我是来偷东西的，我不会伤害任何人。
I'm here to steal, I'm not damaging anyone.
我会的。如果他杀了你，维克，我会捍卫你的荣誉。
I will. If he kills you, Vic, I'll defend your hon our.
艺术只是一种奖励。如果你还想艺术赚钱，
The art'll just be a bonus. If you you wanna still art to make money,
在楼上厨房，那是一个。我告诉过你。
Upstairs in the kitchen, that's the one. I told you.
塞尚。他妈的两亿！不，你没有，我告诉过你。
Cezanne. 200 fucking million! No, you didn't, I told you that.
你对那该死的高脚杯感到兴奋。
You were going gaga about the fucking goblet.
把它拿开，滚开。你他妈的不告诉我该做什么！
Just take it and fuck off. You don't tell me what to fucking do!
去拿吧。
Go and get it.
这是两个人的工作。
It's a two-man job.
那他妈的，你们两个！
Then fucking get it, both of you!
他们要去厨房。对。对。走吧。
They're going to the kitchen. Right. Righto. Let's go.
啊！别做聪明的迪克，弗利。
Ahh! Don't be a clever Dick, Foley.
这些女孩会在你之前得到爆炸。
These girls'll get the blast before you do.
杰克，你想怎么玩？
How do you wanna play this, Jake?
爸爸，我很害怕！没事的，宝贝，会没事的。
Dad, I'm scared! It's OK, baby. It's gonna be OK.
发生什么事？这家伙是谁？
What's going on? Who is this guy?
其他人都在哪里？我们是老朋友。
Where is everyone else? We are old friends.
不是吗，杰克？他是保罗的兄弟。
Aren't we, Jake? He's Paul's brother.
其他人都生病了。生病的
The others are sick. Sick?
什么病了？毒药毒药
Sick from what? Poison. Poison?!
杰克，怎么了？！
Jake, what's going on?!
维克多，你有没有尝试过出售高端被盗艺术品？
Have you ever tried to sell high-end stolen art, Victor?
不管那孩子告诉你什么
Whatever that kid's telling you
艺术收藏家，他们喜欢炫耀。
art collectors, they like to show off.
你要卖给谁？
Who you gonna sell it to?
我有关系，我可以做任何事。
I'm connected, I can fence anything.
你感觉还好吗？
Are you feeling OK?
你看起来不太好。
You don't look so good.
你碰过玻璃了吗？
Did you touch that glass?
是的，是的，我碰了玻璃。那么…那又怎样？
Yeah, yeah, I touched the glass. So... so what?
嗯，你可能对此有问题。
Well, you might have a problem with that.
那就是毒药…在玻璃上的地方。
That's where the poison was... on the glass.
胡说，福莱。为什么玻璃上会中毒？
Bullshit, Foley. Why would there be poisoned on the glass?
我让你问问我即将结婚的妻子妮可。
I'll let you ask my soon-to-be ex-wife Nicole here.
她一直有外遇。我决定毒死她的情人。
She's been having an affair. I decided to poison her lover.
你做了什么？
What have you done?
我不相信你。问她。
I don't believe ya. Ask her.
妮可，你有没有和我的朋友做爱？
Nicole, have you or have you not been fucking one of my friends?
亚历克斯在哪里？
Where's Alex?
亚历克斯在哪里？！你现在能感觉到毒药在起作用，不是吗？
Where's Alex?! You can feel the poison taking hold now, can't you?
就在那里…我有保险箱，
Right there... I've got a safe,
里面有一堆现金和你需要的东西来止毒。
In it is a bunch of cash and what you'll need to stop the poison.
我也需要它。
I need it too.
好吧…我去打开保险箱。
OK... I'm gonna go and open the safe.
一跳，我们都跳。
One jumps, we all jump.
哦，孩子！
Oh, boy!
走，走，走！这是什么？小心
Go, go, go! What's this? Watch out!
抓住他！抓住他！
Get him! Get him!
慢速地慢速地
Slowly. Slowly.
找到他了吗？
Got him?
你以为我会让你拥有这个，你这个蠢货？
You think I'm gonna let you have this, you dumb motherfucker?
如果你死了，我一点也不在乎！
I don't give a shit if you die!
谢谢你的钱。我赢了！
Thanks for the money. I win!
享受你的毒死吧，你这个狗娘养的！
Enjoy your death from poison, you shit cunt!
耶！
Yargh!
到现在为止你自己的屁股，不是吗，弗利？
So far up your own arse, aren't you, Foley?
你一直认为你比别人都好！
You always thought you were better than anyone else!
好吧，我把你留在这里，让这些女人看着你死去！
Well, I'll leave you here so these women can watch you die!
爸爸
Dad!
“生活就是游戏，对吧？
'Life's just the game, right?
一场因果报应、运气和物理的游戏。
A game of karma, luck and physics.
人们并不总是知道。
People don't always get to know.
人们并不总是知道
People don't always get to know
比赛何时结束。”
when the game will finish.'
你准备好了吗？
Are you ready?
'经过反思，
'On reflection,
这是一份礼物。”
it's been a gift.'
我们走吧。”我从来没有被误解过。
Let's go. 'I've never been misguided in understanding.
我们走吧。”我从来没有被误导过
Let's go. 'I've never been misguided in understanding
我们为自己创造机会的方式
that the way we've created opportunity for ourselves
没有影响到其他人的生活。
Hasn't had an effect in the lives of others.
这是牛顿定律的另一条。
That's another one of Newton's laws.
我无法改变这一点。
I can't change that.
但我可以尝试重新平衡。
But I can try to rebalance.
在这种程度上，我一半的财产被分割了
To that extent, half of my estate has been divided
在21个慈善机构和基金会中，希望资金找到出路
amongst 21 charities and foundations in the hope the money finds its way
给那些最需要它的人，
to those who need it most,
包括受赌博成瘾影响的家庭
including families affected by gambling addiction.'
“这是约翰最后的遗嘱…”
"This is the last will and testament of John..."
德鲁，我已经签署了对两家公司的全面控制权给你。
'Drew, I have signed total control over both companies to you.
有一个关于未来利润的时间表
There's a's schedule for future profits
这涉及到这个房间里的每个人。
that involves everyone in this room.
谢谢你所做的一切，伙计。
Thanks for everything, man.
那真是一次骑行。我会再见到你的。”
What a ride that was. I'll see you again.'
“再见。”
"I'll see you again."
保利，你必须退出政治，
'Paulie, you have to get out of politics,
这不是一个健康的地方。
it's not a healthy place.
我希望5000万美元能让过渡变得更容易
I hope $50 million will make the transition easier.'
“妮可和亚历克斯…”“妮可与亚历克斯，5000万美元。
"Nicole and Alex..." 'Nicole and Alex, $50 million.
还有为你所有的孩子设立的基金。
And a fund set up for all your children.
你会成为好父母的。
You're gonna be great parents.
麦克，麦克，麦克。你也有5000万美元。
Mikey, Mikey, Mikey. There's $50 million for you too.
你做得很好，但你必须完成
You're doing great, but you have to finish
你先在康复中心待12个月。这是没有办法的。
your 12 months in rehab first. There's no way around that.
迈克，你可以做任何你想做的事情。
Mike, you can do anything you set your mind to.
丽贝卡，我美丽的女儿。
Rebecca, my beautiful daughter.
对此我很抱歉。
I am so sorry about this.
如果我能改变它，我会的。
If I could change it, I would.
我剩余的财产是你的，这是一大笔钱，
The remainder of my estate is yours, it's a lot of money,
已经在您的帐户中。
already in accounts in your name.
你处理好了，你会没事的。
You manage it, you'll be fine.
我爱你。”我也爱你，爸爸。
I love you.' I love you too, Dad.
“Bec，你的罪孽深重的叔叔绝不完美，
'Bec, your delinquent uncles are in no way perfect,
但你会发现，在生活中，友谊和爱情开始了
but you'll find in life that friendship and love start
当你原谅不完美时。
when you forgive imperfections.
听他们所有人说。他们都有重大的人生旅程可供借鉴。
Listen to them all. They've all got big life journeys to draw from.
但最听德鲁的。
But listen to Drew the most.
善待彼此。
Be kind to each other.
不要做半空半满的人，
Don't be glass half empty or half full people,
做那种知道
be the kind of people who know
无论发生什么胜利或灾难
whatever triumph or disaster comes along
你可以随时给杯子加满
you can always refill the glass.'
♪ 走出一步，感受阳光
♪ Take a step outside and feel the sun
♪ 运气好一点
♪ With a little luck
♪ 这就是你会记得的
♪ That's what you will remember
♪ 当牌打完，手牌打完
♪ When the cards are played and the hand's done
♪ 当比赛结束时
♪ And when... when the game is over
♪ 我会用任何东西换来一个熟悉的吻
♪ I'll trade anything for a knowing kiss
♪ 在永恒的拥抱中
♪ In an embrace that lasts forever
♪ 我像这样紧紧地贴着你的皮肤
♪ I'd pressed tightly to your skin like this
♪ 我们将永远在一起
♪ We will always be together
♪ 我会悄悄地滑向雾霾吗？
♪ Will I slip quietly into the haze?
♪ 我会撕碎闪闪发光的余烬吗？
♪ Will I rage at the shining dying embers?
♪ 我会勇敢地面对它笑吗？
♪ Will I be brave and laugh in its face?
♪ 我会知道整个该死的比赛结束了吗？
♪ Will I even know that the whole damn game is over?
♪ 我愿意用任何东西换取一个熟悉的吻
♪ I'd trade anything for a knowing kiss
♪ 一个永恒的拥抱
♪ And an embrace that lasts forever
♪ 我像这样紧紧地贴着你的皮肤
♪ I'd pressed tightly to your skin like this
♪ 我们将永远在一起
♪ We will always be together
♪ 当光线演化时
♪ When the lights evolve
♪ 当他们及时响起
♪ When they ring in time
♪ 当黑暗来临时
♪ When the darkness comes
♪ 不要让精神崩溃
♪ Don't let the spirit fall
♪ 你不会孤单的
♪ You won't be alone
♪ 我将永远，永远是你的
♪ I will always, always be yours
♪ 我愿意做任何交易
♪ I'd trade anything
♪ 为了一个熟悉的吻
♪ For a knowing kiss
♪ 永远的拥抱
♪ And an embrace that lasts forever
♪ 我会像这样紧贴你的皮肤
♪ I'll pressed tightly to your skin like this
♪ 我们将永远
♪ We will always be
♪ 我们将永远在一起♪
♪ We will always be together ♪